让我们看一下从天气表中读写数据的解答
Let's look at our solution for reading
and writing from the Weather Table.
首先  我们利用testLocationTable()方法返回的
First, we take advantage of
testLocationTable returning
locationRowId来少做一些苦差事
the locationRowId to save
us a bit of drudgery.
但是以防万一  我们还是断言这个方法没有正确返回值
But we assert just in case that function
didn't set the return value correctly.
然后我们遵照和上次一样的步骤  但是使用
We then follow the same steps we did
last time, except we create the weather
从插入位置返回的locationRowId来创建天气数据
values with the locationRowId
we got from the location insert.
然后我们插入数据  查询获取Cursor对象
We then insert the record,
query to get our cursor,
验证Cursor对象并且关闭数据库
validate our cursor,
and close the database.
现在让我们再次运行这些测试  它们都通过了
Now, let's run those tests again,
and they pass.
我们的数据库测试结束了
Our database tests are done.